吸血鬼后裔前情提要
Previously on Legacies.
我今天知道了
I learned today
无论我们多努力
that no matter how hard we try,
也解决不了怪物的问题
we can't solve the monster problem.
所以我得离开神秘瀑布镇
So I have to leave Mystic Falls
就让那些怪物跟随着我
knowing that they'll follow me.
从那个传送门出来的每一个怪物
Every monster that comes out of that portal
都想把他弄回马里之洼
wants him for Malivore.
我不是为了兰登·科比来的
I am not here for Landon Kirby.
你有了新的主人
You serve a new master.
你又是谁
And who the hell are you?
生与死的带来者
Bringer of life and death.
地狱中被诅咒的国王
The cursed king of the underworld.
亡灵巫师
The Necromancer!
一年前
刀子已经被毁灭
Oh, the knife is destroyed.
其中一个锁已经被打开
One lock is released.
意味着
And with it...
我也可以走了
so am I.
喂  你不能睡在这
Hey. You can't sleep here.
我没有睡  你个大呆子
I wasn't sleeping, you thundering dolt!
我是被魔法传送到这个
I was magically transported
这个
here to this...
这什么地方
What is this place?
这是一个单排商业区  你得再被
It's a strip mall. And you're gonna have
魔法传送到其他地方了
to magically transport somewhere else,
这里是私有财产
'cause it's also private property.
你个大虫
Worm!
你知道你在跟谁讲话吗
Do you have any idea to whom you speak?
我可是
I am the...
亡灵
Necro...
马里之洼
What did Malivore
- 对我做了什么啊 -  不知道
do to me? No idea. But if you don't
但如果你不走  我就报警了
leave here, I'm-a have to call the cops.
肃静
Silence!
我的能力呢
My powers.
他把我的能力拿走了
He took them.
但我们说好的
Oh, but we had a deal!
他答应了我的
He promised me!
那就报警咯
Okay, cops it is.
等等  告诉我
Wait. Tell me.
我在安宁吗
Am I in peace?
哥们  你在德州
Buddy, you're in Texas.
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第9集
重新开始
Starting over.
如今
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
理论上来说是容易的
In theory, it's simple.
你抛掉过去
You put the past behind you,
带着你学到的经验  重新开始
take what you learned and begin again.
但做起来并没有说的那么容易
But it's not as easy as it sounds.
翻 译  岛岛
向前走意味着抛掉很多东西
Moving on means letting things go.
熟悉的  简单的  安全的东西
Things that are familiar, easy, safe.
那些重要的东西
Things that matter.
翻 译  银子小狐狸
有人曾说你再也没法回家了
Someone once said you can't go home again.
我真心希望他们说错了
I hope like hell they were wrong.
翻 译  RossyGeng
翻 译  Carousel
只是你啊
It's just you.
阿莉莎  这是干什么
Alyssa, what's all this?
你被人忘却了什么的之后我就搬进来了
I moved in while you were forgotten or whatever.
你睡那半边吧
Your side's over there.
- 我之前都是单人间的  - 对啊
I usually have a single. Which is what
你来之前我也是睡单人间的
I had until this exact moment.
特效：小螺号
我10点就睡觉  所有大晚上不要带人来
I go to bed at 10:00, so no late-night visitors.
我也不想招蚂蚁
And I don't want ants,
所以不要在屋里吃东西
so no eating in the room.
校 对   岛岛
回见了  室友
Later, roomie.
特 效   麦 斯
你是上课要迟到了
You're late for class.
- 还是走丢了 - 都有
Or are you lost? Uh, both.
我不在的时候一切都变了啊
Apparently, everything changed when I was gone.
- 咒语实验室在哪啊  - 不知道
Where's spell lab? No idea.
我自己也有点搞不清楚
I'm a little out of the loop myself.
我就昂首挺胸的跟人点头微笑
I just like to stride confidently and, uh, nod
希望大家不要看穿我吧
in hopes that people don't figure that out.
说的摸不着头脑
But speaking of being out of the loop,
丽兹和乔西都在躲着我  为什么啊
Lizzie and Josie are avoiding me. Why? what's up?
我哪知道
I wouldn't know.
我跟乔西之间还挺尴尬的
Things are still awkward between me and Josie.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我以为没事了
I mean, I thought they were okay.
但又不行了
It's just bad again.
反正吧  知道你和兰登在一起了
Yeah, well, knowing you and Landon
和能够接受理解这件事是不一样的
are together and seeing it are two very different things.
我就是希望我能做点什么
I just wish there was something I could do.
给她点时间吧
You just have to give her some time, you know?
很快一切都会恢复正常的
Things will go back to normal soon enough.
希望吧
I hope.
是啊
Yeah.
咒语实验室
Spell lab. Oh!
里克
Ric. Mm.
我跟卡洛琳透底了
So, I touched base with Caroline. Mm.
她想让我们找到真正的瓦德莫斯
She wants us to track down the real Vardemus
确保他没事  但我更担心的是假的瓦德莫斯
and make sure he's okay. I'm more concerned about the fake Vardemus
在我不在的时候搞了一个500岁的吸血鬼来上学了
enrolling a 500-year-old vampire in my absence.
技术上来说  塞巴斯蒂安有483年
Technically, Sebastian was in a coffin
都是在棺材里的  但那也不行啊
for 483 of them, but yeah.
但我们有招生规则的啊
Yeah, but we have our recruitment bylaws.
是被瓦德莫斯修改过的啊
Which Vardemus revised.
更不用说漫长的录取过程了
Not to mention a lengthy admission process.
已经被他取消了
Which he waived.
你知道他还把咖啡机扔了吗
Do you know that he got rid of the espresso machine?
他更喜欢喝茶
He was more of a tea person.
我得多了解一点这个塞巴斯蒂安
Look, I need to know more about this Sebastian.
不能什么都不了解
We can't blindly let him in here
就盲目的让他入学了
without knowing more about his history.
你说得对
You're right. I'll have
我让我的实习生去看看历史记录
my intern do a deep dive into the historical records
有没有他的线索
to see if there's any trace of him.
你还有实习生呢
You have an intern?
老爸啊
Dad. Hi.
丽兹宝贝
Liz-bear.
你上课要迟到了
You're late for class. Oh.
我分心了
Um, I... I got distracted,
没看表
and I lost track of time.
不过我这样太愚蠢了
But it was... it was dumb
而且很不负责任
and irresponsible, and it will
以后再也不会发生了
never happen again.
如果感到快乐
* If you're happy and you know it *
11个月前
你就拍拍手
* Clap your hands *
如果感到快乐
* If you're happy and you know it *
你就拍拍手
* Clap your hands *
如果感到快乐
* If you're happy and you know it *
那你绝对要拍拍手啊
* Then your face will surely show it *
如果感到快乐
* If you're happy and you know it *
你就拍拍手
* Clap your hands. *
听我说  虫子
Hear me, insect.
这是死亡之主在召唤你
This is the master of death calling to you.
觉醒吧
Rise.
泰德  有空吗
Ted? Got a sec?
今天是疯狂帽子日呢
You know, it's crazy hat day,
你没有戴疯狂帽子哦
and you're not wearing a crazy hat.
我怎么会犯这么愚蠢的错误呢
How could I make such a mistake?
是这样
Look.
我不认为我是你上司
I don't think of myself as your boss.
我认为我是你的朋友
I think of myself as your friend.
但底线是  我需要我的朋友能够按时上班
And bottom line is I need my friends to be on time,
在特殊活动日子进行参与
participate in spirit days
最重要的是
and, most of all,
唱歌
sing...
如果有人往小费罐子里放钱了  就要唱歌
when someone puts money in the jar.
你可以做到吗
Think you can do that?
好的
Sure.
盖里
Gary.
别让他烦到你了  哥们
Don't let him get to you, man.
没人可以烦到我的
No one gets to me.
我就是很生气你知道吧
I just get so mad, you know?
有一次他把我惹急了
One time he pissed me off,
我把他手机放进华夫筒里给烤了
I toasted his phone with the waffle cones.
那是你干的啊
That was you?
你那件事让我这个月
That masterstroke provided me
唯一开心了一次呢
the only smile I've had this month.
厉害了
Sick.
查德
Chad.
我就是
I'm the...
泰德
Ted.
我是泰德
I'm Ted.
嘿  乔
Hey, Jo.
干嘛呢
Uh, what's up?
嘿
Hey.
我给你做了布朗尼
I got you some brownies.
我得走了
Um, I have to run, though.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
I love you. Love you, too.
塞巴斯蒂安  坐
Sebastian. Sit.
塞巴斯蒂安  我们学校的本质
Sebastian, our school was founded
是要让年轻的超能力者
to keep young supernaturals
免受到世界的伤害
safe from the world. Well,
在我看来是让世界免受我们的伤害吧
my impression is that it exists to keep the world safe from us.
这是一种平衡
It's a balance.
听我说
Look,
我本来是不觉得你应该来这里的
I'm not convinced you belong here.
我们这里不收17岁以上的吸血鬼
We don't admit vampires over the age of 17.
但是呢
But...
既然你一直都被关在棺材里
Since you've been stuck in that coffin,
如果你通过考试
I might make an exception
我就给你破个例
if you pass our tests.
所以今天你要花时间
So today you will spend time
面对很多派系
with the various factions. The goal
目标是看看你能否控制住你的基本冲动
is to see if you can control your basic urges.
你知道谁会是一个理想的导师吗
You know who would be an ideal guide
你女儿伊丽莎白
is your daughter Elizabeth.
你离我女儿们远点
You stay away from my daughters.
当是我第一次警告你了
Consider this your one warning.
那要是我那么危险
Well, if I'm so dangerous,
谁来负责测试啊
who shall be administering this test?
唯一一位被杀了之后
The only student who'll come back to life
还能复活的学生
if you kill him.
差不多大家都在这里了
Pretty much everyone gets along here.
虽然这里还有其他超自然学校
Um, there are other supernatural schools, I guess,
但我们是唯一把三个派系有机统一在一起的学校
but we're the only one that integrates all three factions.
对新生来说  可能会有点应付不来
It can be a little overwhelming for new students.
不是三个派系  是四个
'Tis not three factions. 'Tis four.
跟我说说  凤凰有什么力量
Tell me, what powers does a phoenix possess?
当然  除了经常涅槃之外
Surely, it's more than merely dying often.
也就差不多这样了吧  不过我习惯了
That's kind of it. I'm cool with it, though.
其他在这的人都有扮演英雄的角色
I mean, everyone else has the hero angle covered here.
我最好还是从旁协助吧
I'm better as a sidekick. Mm.
我感觉不会那么轻易被杀死
I imagine it would be nice
应该是挺爽的事吧
not to be killed quite so easily.
话说  上次抱歉啦
Sorry about last time, by the way.
没事的
No worries.
你又不是这儿第一个干掉我的人了
You're not the first person around here who's killed me.
怎么样  什么情况
How's it going? What-What's up?
老样子  在我爸
The usual. Getting rid
反应过度之前处理掉那些魔法证据
of magical evidence before my dad overreacts.
- 好的  - 那个  再见啦
Sure. Anyways, see you later.
这是不是就他们说的
Is this what they call
- 青春偶像剧  - 闭嘴吧
"teen drama"? Shut up. Hey.
怎么样
Hey. How's it... Uh, hi.
- 乔西不是因为看到我才走的吧  - 但愿不是吧
Josie didn't leave because of me, right? I hope not.
- 你都搬进来弄好了吗  - 嗯
Um, you're all moved in? Yeah.
阿莉莎·常很慷慨把我房间的五分之一又给我了
Um, Alyssa Chang generously gave me back 20% of my room.
对我还剩下的
Plenty of space
9件东西来说  挺宽敞的了
for the nine things I still own.
- 怎么了 - 萨尔茨曼博士
What's going on? Uh, Dr. Saltzman is having me test
让我测试一下塞巴斯蒂安  看看他能否留在学校
Sebastian here to see if he can stay at the school.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
需要帮手叫我啊
Call if you need backup?
我可以保证  我会老老实实的
I can assure you, I will be on my best behavior.
助手也能搞定我
Even a sidekick can handle me.
这简直是装模作样
This is a charade.
我们不该在这里清洗冻乳品和糖
We shouldn't be here cleaning congealed dairy and sugar.
我们应该是王
We should be kings.
人们听到我们的大名时  应该颤抖
People should tremble at the sound of our names.
布道
Preach.
力量啊  查德
Power, Chad!
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm talking about.
真正的力量
Real power.
- 钱是么  - 不是
Cash money. No!
不是钱  傻子都能一夜暴富
Not money. Any fool can get rich.
是哈
Oh, right.
招魂术
Necromancy.
统治生死
Dominion over life and death.
让全宇宙
The ability to bend
对你俯首称臣的能力
the universe to your will.
就像你之前的活计那样
Like that sweet gig you used to have.
四处转悠  自己当老大
Walking around, being your own boss,
让人们死而复生
raising people from the dead.
你相信我的故事
You believe my story?
当然
Of course.
那些政府不想让我们知道的事
I'm into all that stuff the government
我都信  飞碟啊  蜥蜴人
- doesn't want us to know about-- UFOs, lizard men,
大脚怪这些
Bigfoot.
真希望我能看见你昔日的
I just wish I could've seen you kick ass
不尽雄光
back in the day.
也许还来得及
Maybe you're not too late.
觉醒吧
Rise.
你刚刚是
Did you just...?
我一直在练习
I've been practicing.
现在你见识到我的法术了  我有一个问你
Now you've witnessed my sorcery, I have one question
要问你  查德
for you, Chad.
你愿意做我的侍僧吗
Will you be my acolyte?
当然愿意  侍僧是什么
Hell yeah. What-What's an acolyte?
就是追随者的美化版
It's a fancy word for "follower."
我们要去向何处
Where are we going?
我们要回到过去的
We're going back to the way
那种生活
things used to be.
因为不知怎的
Because somehow...
我要再次成为亡灵巫师了
I'm gonna become the Necromancer again.
7个月前
醒来吧  小猫
Rise, feline.
起来吧
Rise.
应该会花多少时间
: How long's it supposed to take?
我也不知道  查德
I don't know, Chad.
相比更复杂的动物来说
Cockroaches are child's play
螳螂只是小儿科
compared to more complex animals.
最终你还是会回到人类身上施法  对吧
Ev-Eventually you work your way back up to humans, right?
一切刚好  侍僧
All in good time, my acolyte.
马里之洼夺走了我的力量
Malivore took my powers,
但他夺不走与生俱来
but he couldn't take my birthright-
喜爱魔法的权利
a propensity for magic.
现在我需要一步步来再次习得魔法
Now I need to rebuild my skills, step by step.
你为什么觉得是马里之洼干的
Why do you think Malivore did this to you?
如果承诺了给你安宁
Well, if you were promised peace,
他为什么还要送你来这里
why did he send you here?
他肯定是嫉妒我的力量
I'm sure he was jealous of my power.
我是唯一一个聪明到可以智取
That I was the only one who was smart enough to outfox...
奇怪啊
Oh, that's strange.
我记不得从谁那里偷了刀了
I can't remember who I stole the knife from.
我记得生气的那人
I mean, I remember the man with the anger issues
还有他那让人印象深刻的下巴
and the impressive jawline,
但当时还有别人在场
but there was someone else.
所以你看到了所有这些惊人的多重宇宙
So you get to see all of these amazing alternate universes,
但随后  最终  一切就又都归于正常
but then, eventually, everything just resets back to normal,
英雄们都不记得发生过什么了吗
and the heroes don't even remember any of it?
真差劲
Lame.
不得不说  你想出来一起玩我很惊讶
I got to say, I'm surprised you wanted to hang out.
还以为你不会和我说话了呢
I thought you weren't gonna talk to me ever again.
装神弄鬼确实应该被谴责
Gaslighting me was a reprehensible act,
但继续给我讲这些穿紧身衣的超英的事
but keep supplying me with superheroes in spandex,
我们就算扯平了
and we'll call it a wash.
好吧
Okay.
坦白说吧  你
Come clean. You-you hate
- 挺烦看书什么的  - 好吧
all this nerdy stuff. Okay, fine.
我尽力在克制不和塞巴斯蒂安再上床了
I'm trying not to have sex with Sebastian again.
我还以为你也讨厌他呢
I thought you hated him, too.
我是讨厌  但我就是
I did. I mean, I do. I just...
他也同样知道怎么让我爽
I'm also incredibly turned on by him.
- 这些话就别跟我说了  - 我们
- Oh, I don't need to hear any of this. So we're-- we've been
啪过好多次
having a lot of sex.
我的大脑告诉我要停下
And-and my mind is telling me to stop,
但显然我的身体没有接收到
but apparently my body didn't get the message about
我自己有多女权主义者的信息
how much of a feminist I am.
所以在他不可避免被
So I'm trying to avoid him
踢出学校之前  我打算尽力避开他
until he is inevitably kicked out of school.
看漫画书基本上就等于是洗下冷水澡了
And comic books are the literary equivalent of a cold shower.
那实际上是本漫画小说
That's actually a graphic novel.
好的  很好  继续说下去
Okay, yeah, that's good. Keep saying stuff like that.
不  这是一部开创性的小说
No. This is a seminal work of fiction,
不是用来消磨你发情的欲望的
not something to run your horny clock out.
5个月前
快点 兄弟  快起来
Come on, man. Get... get up!
你不能这样无精打采
You-you can't just mope around like this.
你想施法还是干什么吗
You-you want to do magic or something?
没有意义
Hmm. Pointless!
我居然蠢到以为
Ah, I was foolish to think
能重现自己的昔日荣光
I could reclaim my former glory.
我一开始花了
It took me centuries
几个世纪的时间才成为亡灵巫师
to become the Necromancer in the first place!
你不能这样放弃梦想  兄弟
You can't give up on your dreams, man!
你应该奋起反抗
You should fight him.
我们都应该反抗
We both should fight him.
马里之洼现在在哪
Where is Malivore right now?
他是佐治亚州乡下的一个黑洞坑
He's a sentient pit of black goo in rural Georgia.
好的  那我们就朝他撒泡尿
Okay. Well, then we pee on him.
对  我们就尿在里面
Yeah. We take a leak right in that pit.
让他看看谁才是老大
That'll show him who's boss.
对
Yeah.
对啊
Yeah!
- 你有拉夫的消息吗  - 他要和他爸待会
Have you heard from Raf? Uh, he's staying with his dad for a bit.
对他来说应该是好事
I think it'll be good for him.
告诉颧骨队长
Tell, uh, Captain Cheekbones
他这么盯人是个问题了
he's got a weird staring problem.
没事的  多数吸血鬼
It's okay. Lots of vampires
不会在狼人附近  更不用说这么多了
can't be around one werewolf, let alone this many.
大部分吸血鬼控制不了情绪
Most vampires can't control their emotions.
大概是所有力量的缺陷吧
Downside of all the power, I guess.
我觉得没有力量才是问题呢
I think having no power would be far more concerning.
要知道  一个金发美妞告诉了我
You know, a little blonde birdie told me that
卡拉克差点杀了霍普
Clarke almost killed Hope.
她无能为力  拼命逃命
She was powerless and running for her life,
而你
and you were... you were...
你是在寻找自我吗
you were searching for yourself?
我是在保证大家的安全
I was trying to keep everyone safe.
管用吗
And did it work?
当然  也不是说你
Mm. Not that you could have done
什么事都能做
anything anyway, of course,
但如果我爱的女孩有危险
but if the girl that I had loved was in danger,
我希望能够保护她
I would want to be able to protect her.
他也玩
He'll play.
2  3
* Two, three *
我过去常担心自己的行事方式
* I used to worry about the way that I walk *
比如  会不会太吵
* Like, was I talking too loud? *
能不能和运动员一起玩
* And could I hang with the jocks? *
表里不一很难的
* It's never easy to be different inside *
但当你不再在意
* But when you don't give a ... *
一切就像骑单车那么简单
* It's just like riding a bike *
我试图跟他们说再见
* I try to tell 'em "See ya later!" *
我对所有怀恨之人  以爱感化
* I send my love to all the haters *
我只是想让他们知道
* Yeah, I just wanna let 'em know... *
漂亮啊  狼伙计
Well played, my lupine friend.
随时可以重赛  吸血鬼
Rematch anytime, bloodsucker.
没问题
Anytime.
宝贝不会哭
* This baby don't cry. *
这还真挺好玩的
This is fun.
马里之洼
Oh, Malivore!
5个月前
你有客人了
You have visitors.
我们给你带了一个小
We brought you a little pre...
这个洞空了  有人把马里之洼的
Pit is empty. Someone closed
大门关闭了
the portal.
马里之洼被打败了
Malivore was defeated.
你是对的
You were right.
如果马里之洼可以被打败  那什么都是可能的了
And if Malivore can be beaten, anything's possible.
我可以完成我的使命了
I can fulfill my destiny.
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm talking about!
没错
Yeah.
所以我们之后该做什么  我们该怎么让你的能力升级
So-so what do we do next? How do we level you up?
黑巫术需要昂贵的代价
Oh, dark sorcery requires a steep price
才可以换来魔法
to be paid in exchange for power.
我怕是需要献祭出我认为的最珍贵的东西
I'm afraid I must sacrifice that which I hold most dear.
- 那是什么  - 在这个糟糕的世界里唯一一个让我
What's that? The only thing in this wretched existence
感到珍贵的东西就是
I've grown fond of.
觉醒吧
Rise.
重新回到这个世界
Come back to this plane.
4个月前
你活过来了
There you are.
兄弟
Dude.
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
这才是我真实的面容
This is my true face.
注意
Behold
地狱世界的标志
the mark of the underworld.
- 等下  你是杀了我吗  - 理论上是的
Wait. Did you kill me? Technically.
但我本来就打算把你从地狱里带回来
But I always intended to raise you from perdition.
什么  你不应该提前警告我一下吗
What? Shouldn't you have warned me or something?
你没抓到重点  查德
Uh, you're missing the headline, Chad.
我现在可以复活人类了
I can now raise... humans.
我不是僵尸  对吧
Well, I'm not a zombie, though, right?
- 你不能  就是  控制我呢吧  - 穿上这个
You can't, like, control me? Try this on.
- 这是什么  - 图腾
What's this? Iconic!
我必须要成为一个神秘的图腾才可以
I must become a mysterious symbol that both
让我的侍僧们又害怕又着迷
terrifies and intrigues my acolytes.
- 侍僧们  复数吗  - 不用怕  这都是我宏伟的计划的一部分
Acolytes, plural? Fear not. It's all part of my master plan.
- 我在路上再和你说  - 我们要去哪儿
I'll catch you up on the way. Where are we going?
去一个有无尽的魔法能量的地方  一个
To a place of immense magical energy, a place where
有很多人死去的地方  一个充满了
so many people have died, the very ground courses
鲜血和力量的地方
with blood and power.
你去过弗吉尼亚吗
Have you ever been to Virginia?
嘿  格里斯雷  我听说他在和你的女友
Hey, Greasley, I heard he's moving in
暧昧不清
on your girl.
是他吗
Is that him?
她不是我的女友
Well, she's not my girl,
我可以和你还有女巫们坐一起吗
and can I sit with you and the witches?
我今天可不想再和吸血鬼打交道了
I've had enough of vampires today.
你是我们最爱的吸血鬼
Oh, you're our favorite vampire.
如果你讨厌他  我们就讨厌他
If you hate him, we hate him.
他那副德古拉的老式做派让我们所有吸血鬼都显得很不好
He makes us look bad with his old-ass Dracula ways.
那就把他踢出去吗  他今天要进行行为测试
So run him out. He's doing his behavioral tests.
- 让他挂掉  - 怎么做啊
Make him fail. How?
帮我找个创口贴  可以吗
Find me a Band-Aid, will you?
所以  你和那些狼人们挺处的来的
So, you get along with the wolves.
那么我们只需要看看你能不能和这里的吸血鬼们合得来了
Now we just have to see if you fit in with the vampires here.
我们可以在他们吃饭的时候去看看
Uh, we can hang out while they eat.
或者我想也可以说是喝
Or drink, I guess.
当然是动物的血
Animal blood, of course.
当然
Of course.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我手滑了
It slipped.
红色警报  吸血鬼们  都出去  立刻
Code red. Vamps, clear out. Now!
杰德  让你的狼群冷静下来
Jed, calm your pack down.
狼人们  跟我走
Wolves, follow me.
呼吸  密尔顿  呼吸
Breathe, Milton, breathe!
只关注我的声音
Focus only on the sound of my voice.
呼吸  呼吸
Breathe! Breathe.
呼吸
Breathe.
这个冲动会过去的
The urge will pass.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那个女巫  她是故意打碎盘子的
The witch, she broke that plate on purpose.
她和你那个正在成长的开膛手朋友之间
Between her and your... budding Ripper,
你确定我才是那个让人担心的吗
are you sure it is me that you should be worried about?
就是这儿了
This is it.
一个拥有几乎无限的魔法能量的地方
A site of almost unlimited magical power.
3个月前
神秘瀑布镇
我以为会更大点儿的
I thought it'd be bigger.
查德  安静
Chad, please!
我会向大地献祭
I will consecrate the ground.
然后我们会给下一个要从这里走过去的无助的灵魂
Then we will set a trap for the next hapless soul
设下陷阱
who wanders through.
你从没提过这事啊
You never said anything about that.
为了把我和这个地方连接在一起
To seal my bond to this place
然后从这个地方下面的神秘魔法炉里吸取能量
and draw from the mystical hot spot beneath,
我必须要杀人
I'll need to murder.
纯粹的肆无忌惮的
A murder of pure,
残忍谋杀
unbridled cruelty.
你在做啥
What's that?
在克拉克之前假装成为校长瓦德莫斯的时候
Um, an assignment that Clarke had me working on
让我做的一个作业
when he was pretending to be Headmaster Vardemus.
克拉克已经死了  所以我觉得
Well, Clarke's dead, so I'm pretty sure
你不需要再做这个作业了
you don't have to turn that in.
我其实是在想办法摆脱这个东西
I was actually just working on getting rid of it.
所以  应该挺简单的
So, should be easy.
魔法废弃令吗
Magic nullification?
那些都是高级的链接咒语啊
Those are advanced chain spells.
你还需有一个女巫的帮忙
You would need another witch.
是什么样的作业啊
What kind of assignment was it?
我可以帮忙
I can help.
我确定我们可以搞定的
I'm sure we can handle it.
我是说  可能对我们来说是很好的练习机会呢
I mean, it could be good practice for us.
那行吧
Have fun.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但我其实不需要任何帮助
Uh, but I actually don't need any help, so...
丽兹和我说过沙漏的事儿了
Lizzie told me about the Sandclock.
她觉得我可以帮忙
She thought I could help.
怎么帮
How?
我一个朋友文森特告诉过我一个关于泥沼的故事
My friend Vincent told me a story about Mora Miseriums
它可以控制住黑魔法的效果
that hold the effects of black magic,
还有就是如果黑魔法的连接被打破了会有多危险
and how dangerous they can be if they break.
你不会可以从内部让黑魔法无效掉
Look, you can't nullify the black magic inside,
但你可以在外围建上一个保护屏障
but you can put a protective barrier around the outside.
我知道一个很好的咒语可以做到
And I know a good spell for that.
他们建了一个泥沼
Oh... they have a Mora Miserium.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
只要一击  就可以恢复我的力量
In one stroke, it could restore my power.
没错
Yeah.
你还记得那个突然出现在我的记忆里的
You recall the girl who suddenly returned
姑娘吧  那个三派混血
to my memory, the Tribrid?
没错  她可能会是个障碍
Yeah, she'll be an obstacle.
我们可能需要杀了她
We may have to kill her.
或者等我们到那儿了可以把她的朋友也一起全杀掉
Might as well kill all her friends while we're at it, eh?
这是测试的最后一部分了  和女巫相处
This is the final part of the test hanging with the witches.
我要提前警告你  什么也不要碰
Um, I'm warning you, don't push any buttons.
要不你会怎样  在我面前死掉吗
Or you'll do what, die all over me?
你应该担心的不是我
It's not me you should be worried about.
你放松点  女巫都很喜欢我的
Will you relax? Witches love me.
你好  伊丽莎白
Hello, Elizabeth.
嘿
Oh... hey.
是你啊
Oh, you again.
不得不说你愈合的很快啊
I must say you just heal quickly.
是吧  估计是魔法的缘故把
Right? It's like magic or something.
那这个水晶球是什么魔法呢
And what magic is that crystal ball for?
共情状态
Empathic trances.
它可以让我们看到别人埋藏在心底的感受
It lets us read feelings that are buried deep down.
我们可以看看你的吗  吸血鬼的感情都被放大过
Can we read yours? Vampires have heightened emotions.
肯定会是一团乱麻
It'll be a total rush.
我个人  就挺想看呢
I, for one, would like that.
那当然可以了
Then of course.
我确实挺喜欢这些小把戏的
I do love a good parlor trick.
我感觉到
I sense...
恐惧
...fear.
现代世界让你感到恐惧
The modern world is terrifying to you.
你害怕他们不会允许你呆在学校
You're afraid they won't let you stay here at the school.
- 这不是真的  - 你害怕
That's not true. You're afraid
他们会搞清楚你做过的所有事情
they're gonna find out all the things you've done
然后把你扔出去  就像从船里把垃圾扔出去一样
and throw you away, like trash off the side of a boat.
- 停下  - 或许我们应该
- Stop. - Maybe we should...
你知道丽兹要比你好得多
You know Lizzie's better than you
你配不上她
and that you don't deserve her.
停下  停下  让他走吧
Stop! Stop! Let him go.
你是来幸灾乐祸的吗  兰登
Have you come to gloat, Landon?
我只是想来看看你怎么样
I just wanted to see if you were okay.
事实上  我并不好
The fundamental truth is that I am not.
我八岁的时候  我的父母  他们把我卖到
When I was eight years old, my parents, they sold me
商船上了
to a merchant ship.
我恨极了那样的日子
I hated that life,
所以每到一个港口  我都会跑掉
so every port we sailed to, I ran away.
但水手
But the crew,
他们每一次都能找到我
they always found me again.
然后他们为我发明了一个特殊的惩罚
And they devised very special punishments for me.
这是一个残酷的世界  兰登  我也不期待
This is a cruel world, Landon, and I expect
它会给我什么
very little from it.
但伊丽莎白心悦我
But Elizabeth wants me,
我也心悦她
and I want her, too.
但我想既然我没有通过你的测试  这些就都不能重要了
I guess none of that matters now since I failed your test.
- 这其实还有点好看呢  - 我想也是吧
- It's actually kind of beautiful. - I guess.
如果你可以看透层层厄运的话
If you can look past the visions of doom.
谢谢你帮我做这个
Thank you for doing this.
没有你我肯定做不了这个的
I couldn't have done this without you.
不  应该是我谢谢你
No, thank you.
这是我这一整天有过的最正常的感觉了
This is the most normal I've felt all day.
但你知道文森特还告诉了我
You should know Vincent also told me that
沙漏的魔力会随着时间而流逝的
the Sandclock degrades over time.
到某一时刻  无论我们做什么
At some point, it will break down from the inside
它都会自动从内部瓦解的
no matter what we do.
但这样至少会给我们点时间
But this will at least give us some time
想办法化解危机
to figure out how to defuse it.
无尽的黑暗在盘旋
* The endless of darkness is hovering... *
为什么克拉克选了我
Why did Clarke choose me?
你值得信任
You're a trusting person.
而且你比你想象的更强大
And you're more powerful than you know.
这些我都不想
I don't want to be either of those things.
他让我去施黑魔法的那一刻  我的脑袋
The second that he had me doing black magic, my head...
就像不是我的了一样
it's like it's not mine anymore.
我很容易心烦  濒临崩溃
I get upset more easily, I'm on edge.
带走我  带走我
* Taking me, taking me... *
还会嫉妒
Jealous.
不都是魔法造成的
It's not all the magic.
这股力量极其强大
* This pull is astronomical... *
我从马里之洼出来之后
When I got out of Malivore,
就来了这里
um, I came here.
这里是我最想回来的地方
It was the first place I wanted to be.
我堕进无名之渊  暗影之处
* I'm drawn to the unknown, where shadows hide... *
你们是我最想见的人
You guys were the first people I wanted to see.
我就溜进了校园
I snuck onto campus.
我的内心
* Something inside of me... *
你和兰登晚上在磨坊
You and Landon were having movie night, or something,
看电影什么的
at the mill.
- 我看到你们了  - 霍普
- I saw you... - Hope.
你俩都很开心
You both looked so happy.
我好嫉妒啊
And I was so jealous.
极其强烈
* Is astronomical... *
如果当时不巧有人路过的话
If the wrong person crossed my path in that moment,
我想象不到我会把他怎样
I can't imagine the damage I would have done.
你怎么熬过来的
How did you move past it?
我努力向前看
I tried to move on.
也走了很多弯路
And I got a lot of that wrong, too.
很显然
Obviously.
但并不意味着我们没有机会了
But that doesn't mean we can't try again.
极其强烈
* Is astronomical. *
看什么呢
What are you reading?
是多利安给我的书
It's a book Dorian got me.
关于一伙海盗吸血鬼的
It's about a band of marauding pirate vampires.
很刺激嘛
Sounds high concept.
我们完成了旅行  测验
Uh, we finished the tour... tests, whatever.
然后呢
And?
塞巴斯蒂安已经不再危险了
Sebastian's no more dangerous than anyone else at this school.
这很惊喜
Well, I am surprised to hear that.
谢谢你  兰登
Thank you, Landon.
无论值不值得  作为一个偷了魔物
For whatever it's worth, coming from the guy who stole
发动天启的人来说
a magical artifact that kick-started the apocalypse...
有时候人是需要时间改正的
...sometimes people just need a chance to get things right.
第14章
残忍的塞巴斯蒂安
真是个话唠
* Such a motormouth *
毫不在乎她
* Don't care what she's about *
大家都好像
* Everybody's like *
她是终极报复
* She's the last payback *
毫无疑问
* There's not any doubt... *
我从老远
I could hear your music
就听到你的歌了
from miles away. Ah.
你可没这胆量
Oh. I didn't think you had it in you.
你说要杀孩子
You were talking about killing kids.
我必须要阻止你
I had to stop you.
你阻止不了我  查德
You can't stop me, Chad.
你现在受控于我了
You're not in control of yourself anymore.
我不是你的朋友
I'm not your friend.
我永远是你的主人
I'm your eternal master.
跪下
Now kneel.
我好像明白了
I think I figured it out.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
为何马里之洼要这么对你
Why Malivore did it to you.
如果他没欺骗你会怎样
What if he wasn't screwing you over?
如果他把你变成人类给你安宁的机会
What if he made you human to give you a shot at peace?
如果你能好好活着
And if you could have just lived that life well,
你也许就能去那里了
you might have gotten there.
他给你机会重新来过
He gave you a chance to start over.
你却没珍惜  泰德
And you blew it, Ted.
别叫我泰德
Don't ever call me that again.
我叫亡灵巫师
My name is The Necromancer.
你挺开心啊
You seem pleased with yourself.
你怎么找到我的  你觉得我会让你
How did you find me? You think I'm gonna let you
没施定位咒就在学校里乱逛吗
walk around my school without an active locator spell?
我现在知道你是谁了
I know who you are now.
我不会任你在世间散漫
And I can't let you loose in the world.
但吸血鬼也是可以改变的
But I know even vampires can change.
我打算给你个让我打脸的机会
So I'm gonna give you a chance to prove me wrong about you.
但你要遵循我的规则
But you're gonna have to follow my rules.
我不再听从命令了
I don't follow orders anymore.
那你就回棺材去
Then you're gonna have to go back in the box.
我会再出来的
I'll just get out again.
您女儿会放我自由的
And it will be your daughter who sets me free.
是啊  我左右不了她的想法
Yeah, you see, I can control her mind.
这感觉真好啊
Oh, how I love that control.
我上过她了
I've had her, you know.
在学校的每一个角落
All over your school.
没错
Mm-hmm, yes.
无论你去哪 做什么
No matter what you do or where you go,
你都没办法让她防备我
you will not be able to protect her from me.
你会是她那
And you will fail as her father
一次次失败的老父亲
over and over and over again.
唯一的办法就是杀了我
The only way is to kill me.
只需一瞬间  我斩首祭品
And with one swift stroke, I decapitated the decoy.
昨天
马里之洼之子要来了
Now behold the real son of Malivore.
阵已经摆好了  主人
The circle is ready, master.
你这是讽刺的口气吗
Is that sarcasm in your voice?
不能用这样的语气毁了这重要的时刻啊  查德
Let's not ruin this momentous occasion with a tone, Chad.
仙鹤爪递给我
Bring me the Crane's Foot.
好了  马里之洼之子
All right, son of Malivore.
咱们开启传送门吧
Let's make ourselves a portal.
已经看完了吗
Oh. Done already?
好吧  接下来想看什么
All right. So what do you want next?
心情怎样
What's the mood?
今天糟透了
Today sucked.
你有推荐吗
You got anything for that?
看看哈
: Let's see.
我有预感你的生活马上
I got a feeling your day's about to get
会好很多
a lot better.
没错
Yeah.
你见过我的新实习生了吗
Have you met my new intern yet?
你很骄傲
* You're proud *
但我需要你时却冷却
* But you're cold when it counts... *
凯姆
Kym.
我应该早点找你帮忙的
I should have asked for help sooner.
我好担心沙漏会碎
I was so worried that the Sandclock would break,
那些魔法都会回到我身上
and all that magic would come back to me
我就会一直伤害别人
and I'd end up hurting someone.
但并没有
But it didn't.
我们都平安无事
We're all safe.
我知道
I know, and, um,
我没问是因为以为看到你和霍普在一起
I didn't ask because I thought that I'd be okay
我能接受的
seeing you and Hope together,
但事实上我感到非常孤独
but it actually kind of just feels, like, really lonely.
就像我在最需要别人
And it's... kind of just what I do.
却推开他们时的感觉一样
I push people away when I need them most.
我是个可笑的人
Because I'm ridiculous.
让你听听我今天有多可笑会不会好受点
Would it make you feel better to hear how I was ridiculous today?
好啊
Yeah.
塞巴斯蒂安被女巫下咒时
When Sebastian flipped out on the witches,
我意识到自己无能为力
I realized there was nothing I could do to help.
我不是学校的英雄
I'm not one of the heroes here,
以前觉得自己没关系的
and I thought I was okay with it.
但现在说不好
But now I don't know.
现在成为英雄还不晚
It's not too late to become one.
你并不荒唐啊
And you are not ridiculous.
我好怀念这样和你聊天
I missed talking to you like this.
希望我们能做朋友
I want us to be friends.
不是男女朋友
Not like ex friends,
而是真正的朋友
like actual friends.
不错啊
: That sounds nice.
这是怎么回事
What's all this?
把我雕刻成
* Carve me up into... *
搞了点小东西让你有家一样的感觉
Just a little something to make you feel more at home.
直到沦为有你气息的碎片
* To choose, till I'm only pieces of you *
这样你就会爱我
* So you can say you love me, but... *
和我们预期的不太一样  但我们想
It's not exactly how it was, but we thought maybe
稍作改动也许你会更喜欢
you might like it if we changed it up a little bit.
这样你就能爱我
* So you can say you love me *
但言语怎能足够
* But words ain't enough. *
爸
Dad.
你把塞巴斯蒂安赶走了  是吗
You kicked Sebastian out, right?
我给他机会遵循我的规矩
I gave him the option to follow the rules.
但他
But he,
选择离开
he chose to leave instead.
是他不想留下咯
So he didn't want to stay.
是
No.
好吧
Good.
挺好的
That's-that's good.
说真的  听说他走了我还挺解脱
Uh, honestly, I, I'm just relieved that he's gone.
不 是好事
: No, i-it's good.
这是好事
It's a good thing.
对不起
: Oh, I'm sorry.
此刻
我什么也看不出来
I don't see anything.
我能
I do.
你好
Hello there,
我的新朋友
my new friend.
马里之洼承诺你安宁是吗
Malivore promised you peace, didn't he?
我有个更好的条件
I have a much better offer.
我可以让你
I can grant you
自由永生
freedom from death.
你只需要
All you have to do
去趟塞尔瓦托学校
is pay a visit to the Salvatore School
把我要的东西拿回来
and bring me back what I need.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）